# MARIAYE VICKERY



JR. UI/UX DESIGNER

## **ABOUT**

I am a Jr. UI/UX designer and experienced arts manager. I have worked as an artist and arts manager for 8 years and recently discovered that my natural design proclivities could lead to a new career in UI/UX. Having recently completed the Google UX Design Certificate, I am seeking an internship or Jr. UI/UX position. I enjoy clever, clean design that meets user's needs. I am motivated to continue improving my understanding and practice of UI/UX design and would love the opportunity to bring this motivation to your

## CONTACT

O Victoria, BC

250-883-8123

mariaye.vickery@gmail.com

mariayevickery.com

dribbble.com/marsvic

Bē behance.net/mariayevickery

### **EDUCATION**

2021 Google UX Design Certificate

Coursera — 2 Month Online Certificate

2014 - 2018 Honours BA, Arts Management

University of Toronto

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2019 - 2020 Gallery Manager

Mountain Galleries

Inventory management, fine art sales, installations and client care. Web design and social media

management.

2018 - 2019 Events Coordinator & Gallery Associate

Arta Gallery

Private event bookings, exhibition curation and art sales. Designing promotional material and social

media management.

2018 - 2021 **Web Developer** 

Freelance

Web design and consultation. Creating online

portfolios and stores.

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE & TECHNOLOGIES

Project Management Figma UX Design

Events Management Adobe XD Graphic Design

Inventory Management Procreate Fine Art Sales